<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Object Detection</string>

    <string name="title_section1">Motion Track</string>
    <string name="title_section2">Color Detect</string>
    <string name="title_section3">(Beta)Counter</string>
    <string name="title_section4">Bounding Box</string>
    <string name="title_section5">Edge Detection</string>


    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_help">Help</string>
    <string name="action_about">About</string>

    <string name="about_text">

        \nDevelopment by:
                      \n\n\tTyler D\'Spain
                        \n\tTony McDonald
                        \n\tDavid Harvey
                        \n\tDaniel Stenbro\n\n



        \nAndroid OpenCV library:
        \n-Version 2.4.11

    </string>
    <string name="help_text">

        <b>Motion Tracking</b> - Motion Tracking illuminates the changing contours in video frame.
                          \n>><i>To set up: Place device steady and wait for background noise to dissipate.
                          Objects moving in view will illuminate in a bright pink color.</i>\n\n

        <b>Color Detection</b> - Color Detection will place a bounding box around the color detected by user.
                          \n>><i>To set up:  Touch screen on area to get color sample.  Once selected objects
                          of that color in the spectrum will be placed inside a green bounding box and tracked.</i>\n\n


        <b>(Beta)Counter</b> - Counter captures any moving object and will place a bounding box around object and once the object
                        passes the count line, the counter will be updated by 1
                        \n>><i>To set up:  Place device steady and wait for background noise to dissipate
                        Objects moving will be placed inside a blue bounding box and will update the count and change
                        counter line display red once the center passes the counter line threshold.</i>\n\n

        <b>Bounding Box</b> - Bounding Box will place a purple stationary box in center of screen, once user selects a object color to track
                       the object will then have a cyan bounding box around it, once it enters entirely inside the stationary box
                       it will then change to a red and display "Captured".
                       \n>><i>To set up: Touch screen on area to get color sample.  Once selected objects of that color
                       in the spectrum will be placed inside a cyan bounding box and tracked.  Move the device to
                       place the object tracked inside the stationary purple box.</i>\n\n

        <b>Edge Detection</b> - Edge detection will find all edges in camera view and only display the picture with the edges highlighted in
                         a blackscreen view
                         \n>><i>To set up: Pan device around to watch the edges detected in real time in the view.</i>

    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_main">Object Detection</string>

</resources>
